https://tagaroom.com/policies/

Skip to content
MENUMENUHOMEMOVING PRODUCTS
Pack N Move LabelsColor Dots & RectanglesMark-It® Dot LabelsClothing LabelsOffice LabelsMoving SuppliesTapes + DispensersMove by Color SystemsSmooth Move SystemsDisplay KitsLoan Approval GiftsBundle Discount's
PACKAGING SUPPLIESABOUT USCONTACT
POLICIES
CART
About UsTag-A-Room is the original creator of the color coded moving and storage label systems. Tag-A-Room was created over 30 years ago by the owner of a small moving company in San Antonio, Texas, to differentiate his company from other moving companies. He used labels to organize the boxes and furniture throughout the move process, thus reducing the chance of having mismarked, misplaced boxes which resulted in customers’ saving of time and money. There was no more asking “Where does it go?”.
30 years later, Tag-A-Room has grown into its own company serving customers nationwide with hundreds of line items. Tag-A-Room provides “Moving and Storage Solutions” to various clients that include: move managers, moving companies, mortgage companies, realtors, retail outlets, and of course our original customer “the end user”. Our products are unique and cost effective, but most importantly they help relieve some of the stress associated with moving, by providing a smooth more organized move experience.
Customer Service PolicyTag-A-Room is committed to providing our customers with extraordinary products, value, service. We strive to provide a seamless, satisfying shopping experience for all our customers by, listening to their needs, evaluating the feedback, and ongoing process development. You can contact our dedicated Tag-A-Room support team at admin@tagaroom.com for an email response with 1 business day. If you need to reach us by phone, please contact us during customer service hours: Mon – Fri 9:00 am – 5:00 pm Central Standard Time.
Shipping PolicyTag-A-Room’s shipping policy includes: We ship next business day following the receipt of order. We ship within the Continental U.S. only. For orders to Alaska, Hawaii, U.S. Protectorates, and to APO/FPO destinations, please contact us for additional charges. Estimated delivery time is 3-5 business days. We are not responsible for weather delays or any unforeseen carrier delays.
Return PolicyReturns may be made within 30 days of order. Returns must be in original package and must be complete. Any product received in error or damaged must be reported with 7 days of receipt. Returns made by customer that are not the fault of the seller will be made at customers expense. Returns may incur a 15% restocking fee.
Privacy PolicyTag-A-Room is committed to protecting your privacy. In order to best serve you, Tag-A-Room may need to gather some personal information from you including but not limited to: Your name, address, telephone number, email address, etc. Your personal information is stored in a secure location and is not accessible to the public. Tag-A-Room does not sell, rent release, or trade personal information to outside parties. Tag-A-Room reserves the right to disclose information, if necessary, to comply with legal investigations or proceedings. Tag-A-Room reserves the right to make necessary changes to its privacy policy at any time, and such changes will be displayed on any and all associated websites.
TAX POLICYWE CHARGE SALES TAX IN THOSE STATES WHERE WE HAVE A PHYSICAL OR ECONOMIC NEXUS
